PENNY:
You know what, hang on.
(Penny:)What if Sheldon had no choice
(Penny:)but to be respectful?
(Leonard:)Is there a switch on the back
of his neck we don't know about?
PENNY:
No.
(Penny:)What I'm saying is you could add
a clause to the contract
(Penny:)that he can't make fun
of Howard.
(Bernadette:)How would you enforce it?
(Sheldon:)Oh, please.
Any contract I sign
(Sheldon:)is enforced by my own
personal code of ethics.
(Amy:)And his obsessive-compulsive
disorder.
(Sheldon:)Yeah, that, too.
(Sheldon:)And scoot over.
(Sheldon:)Part of your shadow's
on my spot.
(Leonard:)Howard, what do you think?
(Howard:)I'm on board.
(Sheldon:)I'll add it right now.
Oh, baby, it's addendum time!
(line ringing)
EMILY:
Hello?
(Raj:)Hey, Emily, listen,
(Raj:)I've been thinking,
and I'm not sure
(Raj:)it's a good idea
that I come over.
(Howard:)Oh.
(crying):
Okay. I understand.
(Raj:)No, no. Please don't cry.